<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidBoilerPlate</string>

    <!-- Activity labels -->
    <string name="label_main">Boilerplate</string>

    <!-- Main Activity -->

    <string name="action_github">View on GitHub</string>
    <string name="text_view">View</string>
    <string name="text_collections">Collections</string>
    <string name="text_no_description">No description available</string>

    <!-- Character Activity -->

    <string name="text_lorem_ipsum">The classic adventures of Spider-Man from the early days up until the 90s. This is where youll find all the big-time action, major storylines and iconic Spider-Man magic youd come to expect from the Wall-Crawler. Now, hes a premiere member of both the X-Men and the Avengers. Born with super-human senses and the power to heal from almost any wound, Wolverine was captured by a secret Canadian organization and given an unbreakable skeleton and claws. Youve found it.\n\n
    Looking for the one superhero comic you just have to read. The classic adventures of Spider-Man from the early days up until the 90s. Youve found it. Born with super-human senses and the power to heal from almost any wound, Wolverine was captured by a secret Canadian organization and given an unbreakable skeleton and claws. Treated like an animal, it took years for him to control himself.\n\n
    Treated like an animal, it took years for him to control himself. Meet all of Spideys deadly enemies, from the Green Goblin and Doctor Octopus to Venom and Carnage, plus see Peter Parker fall in love, face tragedy and triumph, and learn that with great power comes great responsibility. Now, hes a premiere member of both the X-Men and the Avengers. Marvels mighty mutants go worldwide and beyond in this series following Cyclops, Wolverine, Beast, Emma Frost and more in their astonishing adventures. Youve found it.\n\n
    Meet all of Spideys deadly enemies, from the Green Goblin and Doctor Octopus to Venom and Carnage, plus see Peter Parker fall in love, face tragedy and triumph, and learn that with great power comes great responsibility. This is where youll find all the big-time action, major storylines and iconic Spider-Man magic youd come to expect from the Wall-Crawler. Youve found it. Now, hes a premiere member of both the X-Men and the Avengers. Amazing Spider-Man is the cornerstone of the Marvel Universe.</string>

    <!-- Detail Fragment -->

    <string-array name="detail_fragment_titles">
        <item>Comics</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Stories</item>
        <item>Events</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="text_no_data">No data to display</string>

    <!-- Dialogs -->

    <string name="dialog_action_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="dialog_error_title">Oops</string>
    <string name="dialog_general_error_Message">There was an error making the request</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_no_connection">Sorry, you need a connection to do that!</string>



    <integer-array name="avengers">
        <item>1009610</item>
        <item>1009368</item>
        <item>1009351</item>
        <item>1009338</item>
        <item>1009664</item>
        <item>1009187</item>
        <item>1009189</item>
        <item>1009220</item>
        <item>1009297</item>
        <item>1011490</item>
        <item>1009215</item>
        <item>1009524</item>
        <item>1009562</item>
        <item>1009697</item>
        <item>1009707</item>
        <item>1009719</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>
